Hello hello everyone today we will give you
a new critical illness policy from Star Health Insurance
Star Critical Illness Multiple
Insurance Policy Star Health
Insurance has launched a new product called its pocket money
which has
very good features in the credit balance plate you can
subscribe and at the speed at which
our country will mix you subscribe to it
before subscribing to anything else I want to introduce you to
my name I have been
associated with the industry for the last 12 years
if you want to keep yourself updated then
we regularly share information on investment regarding information on the channel
so do subscribe to this channel let's
start reviewing the product talking about entries
anyone weighing 8265 can take this policy
this policy is available only for individual person the policy
is between 5 lakh to 25 and
if someone is between 18 years to 35 years
then you can take it on your Instagram
subscribe
members ki war
₹1500000
subscribe second group is
like and
subscribe
Torch Light Permanent Paralysis Kumawat
Specific Severity Extra Fourth Group
is Major Organ and Dermal Considerations
Compound
Diseases You can check on the screen
and you can click once a year for the maximum group
which the company will
do till now Only one is available in each group
After clicking, you can appoint a
waiting period of 1 month
until you subscribe You
can renew this policy You can
also take it in this piece which can get a
discount up to If you point in this then
you will get a 2% discount
Up to 360 150 You
get a huge discount of 70% The company
gives you an additional benefit for maintaining a healthy lifestyle which is
available for just 80 seconds You can audition
and the online application of Star Health Insurance Company
checks your fitness parameters It has a lot of parameters
like your attractiveness If you
deliver around 5000 to 6000 runs every day then
you will get this point The company if you do eight
to 10  If you subscribe for between Rs 1,000 then there
is a company and if you
can subscribe then you have to subscribe to the company
and apart from this, if you do it for weight management
then there is a
subscription in
between then you can avail caffeine benefit in it, you will have to
share the information every two days, you
can also get points on the weights assessment like your blood sugar
level, haemoglobin, fasting sugar etc.
If you submit a test then the company
can now avail benefits of more than Rs 150, in this way
you
can subscribe on your premium by fulfilling different parameters, you
can also add tele consultation in this plan which has become
very popular, if
you talk about the waiting period of first noida, waiting period for any
kind of appointment, subscription is compulsory, if the
policy holder has any
problem and before 15 days the
company will not accept the death claim of the policy holder, then
subscribe by doing a medical check up, if the
policy holder is less than 50 years then there is no
pre policy medical check up, if above 50 years then there is
a mister policy medical
check up as per the policy terms of  You can
take Splendor for one year, two years, Note for 3 years.
Like every policy, this policy
also has some experiences which we are putting on the screen,
you can check. If
you face any critical illness due to any drink, alcohol or drugs,
then the company will
not file a claim. Even in case of suicide, the
company does not make any claim. No one is
life-long in this plan. This company will
not have to contact any other company for claim. You can avail star health
benefits. If you
feel that you can
cancel the subscription and get your money.
Subscribe and like the Critical Illness Multiple
Insurance Policy. If you
liked the video, then
we keep bringing such information, so
please like and subscribe to our channel.
Thank you for watching.